

SYLWIA DLUZNIEWSKA

- +45 50 20 15 00
- dluzniewska@gmail.com
- sylwiakarolina.com

ABOUT

Recent gradute from the Copenhagen School of Design and Business in **Design technology** and **Sustainable fashion**. Former **studio intern** at Kate Sheridan (UK), and **graphic design** intern at Le Neu Black (DK). Worked as part-time **designer assistant** in Base Range (DK). Past experience in English teaching to kids and adults (PL).

LANGUAGES

Polish
English
Danish
Spanish

CHARACTERISTICS

- basic HTML and CSS
- cat. B driving licence
- creativity
- quick learning ability
- work under pressure
- good team member
- systematic

HOBBIES













EDUCATION

2007-2012

Linguisitics

Master of Arts Gdansk, PL

2012-2014

Design technology

Academic Profession Copenhagen, DK

2014-2016

Sustainable fashion

Bachelor of Arts Copenhagen, DK

WORK EXPERIENCE

2010-2012

English lecturer

private language schools Trojmiasto, PL

3-6.2014

Graphic designer

internship, Le Neu Black Copenhagen, DK

2014-2015

Designer assistant

part-time, BASERANGE Copenhagen, DK

Studio assistant

6-9.2015 internship, Kate Sheridan London, UK

SKILLS











